Does this mean it's a peaceful world now?
Oh, you're awake already!
Morning, big brother!
Kotori! You're all right?!
What about Fraxinus? Is the whole crew okay?!
Are you still half-asleep?
Uh, um... What day is it today?
Huh? What else but November 3rd?
If it's November 3rd, then...
It's the day after Origami went Inverse.
Thank goodness. For real...
Wh-What?!
I managed to change the world after all.
Daily life. An illusion which lasts forever.
What will be illuminated by
the light which was reclaimed?
"Episode Ten:
'Another World, Another Girl'"
You came, Shido! Good morning!
Morning. Sorry to make you wait.
Here, don't freak out.
It's one of your favorites.
Ooh! You made bite-size
cutlets for me today, right?
--Huh?
--Hmm? Isn't that what you said
you'd make yesterday?
Yesterday?
Oh, that's right! Sorry, but I
kinda ran out of ingredients.
I made you a rice bowl today.
With sweet eggs.
M-My word! That sounds the best!
--Ooh! I just ate breakfast, but I'm
feeling hungry just thinking about it!
--Does this world have
a history I'm not aware of?
What a nice morning.
Good on you to pick me up, servant.
Bow. Good morning.
Shido. Tohka. Kotori.
Y-Yeah. Morning.
What's up with you?
For a second there, your eyes were
lingering on Yuzuru and my breasts.
Explanation. That's a perfectly
normal reaction for a man.
Care to comment, Shido?
N-No, I wasn't!
Origami hasn't come yet?
What's the matter?
For one reason or another,
something seems incomplete.
It's a weird feeling.
Incomplete?
Good morning, everybody!
Suzuhara?
Here!
Setouchi?
--Here.
--Is she absent today?
--Takizawa?
--Here.
--Or maybe she's just late?
--Tsukui?
--Here!
--Or maybe she's just late?
Next is Tonomachi.
Here, here!
Hiroto Tonomachi is doing
wonderful again today, my honey!
Marking Tonomachi as present.
Next is Nakahara!
What?
Hmm? Did I say something odd?
Uh, um...
After Tonomachi should be...
Ms. Okamine, what about Origami?
Origami?
Who might that be, may I ask?
Origami? Is that supposed to be a name?
Did Itsuka fold a bunch of
paper cranes for the teacher?
Wha?! He's trying to complete
the Tammie route now?!
That's so lame.
--Nishikubo?
--I see...
--Here
--Negishi?
--I guess in this world, Origami doesn't live in this city.
--Here.
--I guess in this world,
Origami doesn't live in this city.
--Nonohara?
--I guess in this world,
Origami doesn't live in this city.
--Here.
--I guess in this world,
Origami doesn't live in this city.
The Origami of this world doesn't
hold a grudge against Spirits...
...and lives happily with her parents.
It's better this way.
This is how the world should be.
Shido?
What's up, Tohka?
What's wrong? Are you in pain?
Huh?
No, I'm fine.
It's better like this.
Though, I'd have liked
to see her just once...
The Origami of this world, smiling...
What's the matter with Shido?
Yeah, he seems in the dumps.
If he's that zoned out, it's a girl.
Wha--?! What do you mean by that?!
Well, I might be wrong. Don't worry.
If you know something, out with it!
Wh-When it comes to the
troubles of high school boys,
it's almost always about girls.
Girls spreading weird rumors...
Treating them cruelly...
Guys worry about those sorts of things.
Really? Is that how it is?
Yeah. And when you ask
to group up for a project.
They say "Eww" in a disgusted tone.
Or when you pick up their eraser,
they say "I don't want it anymore. Keep it."
H-Hold your horses!
How does a Spirit like you know
so much about student life?
Anyway, I think it's obvious that
something happened to him at school.
He'll probably be fine if we
give him some time, but...
But, it's tough seeing Shido acting so down.
Can't we do something for him?
I don't know what to tell you.
If it's girl trouble giving him grief,
it'll take a girl to heal his heart.
That was close.
I've gotta focus.
Sh-Shido, I'll help.
Okay, thanks.
Then why don't you--
What kinda outfit is that?!
And what's with those bodies?
W-What's it matter to you?
That's right. What's important
is to let us help you out.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha--?!
Natsumi! Is this your doing?!
Wait a damn second!
Why aren't you in a swimsuit?!
We agreed to do this together!
Yeah, but well...
When I thought about it, wearing that
would be way too embarrassing.
I'd feel so stupid, you know.
You're the one who gave us
these stupid outfits!
--You little...! We'll
make you wear one, too!
--Kotori, calm down!
--You little...! We'll make you wear one, too!
Ahh, I'm being violated!
Would you all just...
You guys are killing me.
Hmph. Sorry about that.
I'm sorry, Shido.
Sorry.
Nah, sorry to worry you all.
Thanks. I'm better now.
I don't intend to pry or anything,
but get a hold of yourself.
You never know when
another Spirit will appear.
Yeah.
There's Spirits we don't know about,
not to mention Kurumi and Devil are out there.
Devil? What's that Spirit?
What are you talking about?
The Spirit Hunter "Devil."
Compared to "Nightmare" Kurumi Tokisaki,
she's every bit as dangerous.
As much as Kurumi?
Are you for real? What's with you today?
It's like you forgot everything
up until yesterday!
Would you mind explaining again?
About this Spirit named "Devil."
Devil. We've confirmed she exists, but...
She's an unidentified Spirit who's
evaded all attempts of contact.
Also, and quite likely in fact,
she's an Inverse.
What do you mean?
An Inverse Spirit just
showing up like normal?
I'm trying to tell you,
we don't know a whole lot.
What did you mean by "Spirit Hunter"?
Just like it sounds.
Devil never appears on her own.
It's only when some other
Spirit happens to manifests...
...that she appears and attacks them.
If Tohka and the others hadn't helped,
Natsumi would've been in big trouble.
This is... Devil?
Yeah.
Origami...
Shido, are you still sleepy?
I'm fine. Just didn't get
much sleep last night.
Oh...
Origami...
Origami wasn't in her apartment...
...nor at the house she
lived in with her parents.
Why did she become a Spirit?
Why an Inverse?
By changing history five years back,
I should've saved her parents.
Good morning, everyone!
Let's go all out today!
What could've happened in this
world in that five-year span?
Oh, before I forget!
I can't do much alone...
If I explain what I know,
Ratatoskr might look into it...
Today I have a new friend
to introduce to you all.
Come on in please!
--Whoa, check her out.
--Wonder what she's like?
She's so pretty...
Huh?!
I'm Origami Tobiichi.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
That dazzling long hair
and pure, innocent smile!
Cute enough to give my honey
a run for her money!
Let's see... The seat next to Itsuka is open.
You can sit there.
All right.
No way...
You're...
Eh?
What do you mean? What makes you think
Devil transferred to your school?
I'll explain later once I'm home.
But it's true. Please believe me.
All right, but I'm not thoroughly convinced.
Kotori...
I'll have Ratatoskr investigate.
What's the student's name?
Origami. Origami Tobiichi.
Hold on... Origami Tobiichi from the AST?
What? You actually remember
the last world now?
Huh? What are you talking about?
She's fought against Tohka
and the others a bunch of times.
But she retired not too long ago.
Now that you mention it,
Origami Tobiichi left the AST around
the time Devil first started appearing.
Why did Origami join the AST
if I saved her parents?
Are you even listening?
Oh, sorry. Tell me if you find anything out.
If I changed what happened five
years ago, why is this Origami...?
I might just have to ask her in person...
Um, what's this?
"I want to talk with you.
Come to the roof during lunch.
Itsuka"
You wanted to talk with me?
Yeah, sorry if this seems sudden, Origami.
Huh?
Oops, sorry! I mean Tobiichi.
It's kinda rude of me to call you that.
No, I just wasn't expecting it.
Um, Itsuka...
What's this about?
Tobiichi... Didn't you say something
when you saw me this morning?
Oh! Sorry if that's been bothering you!
I was a little surprised...
You look exactly like someone
I met a long time ago.
Huh?
You mean, could we have...?
No, that's not it.
The person I met was
back some five years ago.
You would've been in elementary school.
Besides...
That person passed away.
Five years ago, right before my eyes...
I see...
Back then...
May I go back to class now?
Uh, wait. Hold on a sec.
Five years ago...
You mean during the Nankou area fire?
How did you...?
Could that have been your big brother I saw?
Well, something like that.
Tobiichi?
Your brother was the one
who saved both of my parents.
If he hadn't been there,
both of them would've died for sure.
I'm forever grateful.
Y-Yeah...
In other words, I was able to
save Origami's parents after all...
Sorry for blurting that out.
No, it's fine.
I'm so thankful for what he did that day.
Unfortunately, my parents died
in a car accident four years ago.
But thanks to your big brother,
for that year they were alive,
my dad and mom gave me so much.
I see...
Is that fate at work?
Itsuka?
But...
Then, why did you join the AST?
If your parents survived...
How do you know about that?!
Uh, um... Well...
Don't tell me you went outside
during a spatial quake alarm!
Uh, yeah. Actually...
That's very dangerous! You have to evacuate!
R-Right.
You want to know the reason I joined the AST?
Yeah. If you don't mind telling me.
Itsuka, you knowing about the AST means...
...you know the reason for the alarms.
Spirits.
During the fire five years ago,
it was a Spirit that killed your big brother.
But that's...
I thought to myself...
...I didn't want more victims
like him to be made.
I wanted to become a person who
could protect others from Spirits.
It's because of what I did then...
Can I ask one more thing?
What's that?
Why did you... become a Spirit?
Huh? What are you talking about?
What's this mean?
That had to be...
Lunch time is over, so...
Thank you. I'm glad we had this talk.
Wait! Can't we talk some more?
But class is about to start.
Some other day is fine.
If you're free sometime, can I see you again?
Huh? Are you asking if...?
Eh?! U-Um...
Could I have some time to think about it?
Uh, of course.
All right, goodbye!
What a strange feeling it is...
Am I too used to how Origami was before?
Shido, where did you go during lunch?
I got a call from Kotori.
She's fine with curry for dinner.
Ooh, that's great! I can't wait for it!
"I'm free this Saturday.
Tobiichi"
Saturday, huh?
I'll have to talk with Ratatoskr.
Man, I'm tired. I'll just rest for a bit...
My goodness.
Big boys should watch
where they sleep, dear Shido.
Whoa! K-Kurumi?!
Good evening, Shido.
Such a cute sleeping face you have.
My goodness. I'm deeply hurt
that you fear me so much.
I thought we were comrades
who changed the world together.
Kurumi, you...
Yes, I remember everything.
About the original world. About Origami, too.
I see...
Why did things end up this way?
What happened to Origami?
That's something even I'm not aware of.
However...
With Origami as she is now,
there are certain ways to find out.
Really?!
Indeed.
Come now, don't be so afraid.
If I just shoot Yod at Origami,
I'll be able to see what sort of life
she lived out in this world.
Yod...
Oh, yeah!
But in that case,
why didn't you use Yod on Origami
when she went Inverse?
My goodness. You think
I could get close to her then?
A-Anyways, we can find out why
she inversed in this world, right?
Please, I need your help.
Whatever shall I do?
Where could it be?
How could I lose my hair clip like that?
What if...?
I knew it! This is where it was!
Thank goodness! I need to be careful...
Hmm?
But in that case...
Is that Itsuka's voice?
Itsuka and...?
Huh? Origami?
Uh, you see... I can explain...
Origami?
My goodness.
Since we're in this world now,
do I say "Nice to meet you?"
Though, it is quite possible we've
already ran into each other before.
Spir... it...
Spirit armor?!
I knew you had to be Devil!
Satan.
Wouldn't you say that's a pretty
violent way to greet someone?
K-Kurumi!
O-Origami, how could you!
What's the meaning of this?
Huh?
Itsuka?
What are you doing in a place like this?
"Episode Eleven:
'Angel of the Starry Night'"